Cong (Cody) Liu

codyliu881@gmail.com | 0450 150 881 | Holding Valid Work Permit

My Personal Website | <u>GitHub</u> | <u>LinkedIn</u>

CAREER SUMMARY

As a front-end web engineer with a passion for development and experience in both freelance and agency settings, I have built websites using various technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, and CMS such as WordPress. My background as an educator has honed my interpersonal skills and ability to communicate effectively.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer | Ionata Digital

Oct 2022 - Jan 2023

- Led the development of the website for TasBulk using a tech stack of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and AWS. The URL is: https://tasbulk.com.au/
- Provided support for troubleshooting previously-built websites with 10 assigned tickets.

Freelance Web Developer

Aug 2022 - Present

- Collaborated with clients to discuss project requirements, provided updates and addressed any issues that may arise.
- Created a website from scratch for an accounting firm, using HTML, CSS and JavaScript from website design to final deployment. The URL is: http://accotaxadvisory.com.au/

Educator | Child's Play Early Learning | Hobart

Jun 2021 – Jun 2022

- Implemented daily routines and educational activities that support children's development.
- Built positive and supportive relationships with children and their families.

3D Printer Trainer | Choc Edge | China

Feb 2016 – May 2019

- Conducted technical training and provided support for clients using chocolate 3D printers.
- Experimented 3D slicer software with adjusting parameters to achieve optimal printing outcomes.
- Collaborated with the development team on a Drawing Application on Android-operated pad.

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- React.js & Next.js
- Bootstrap and Tailwind
- GitHub

- RestAPI
- CMS such as WordPress
- Docker and AWS

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATION

Udemy 2021 - present

The Complete Web Development Bootcamp

The Complete JavaScript Course: From Zero to Expert

Crash Course: Build a Full-Stack Web App in a Weekend Become a WordPress Developer: Unlocking Power with Code Build Responsive Real-World Websites with HTML and CSS Ultimate AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner - 2023

National Institute of Education and Technology

2019 - 2021

Advanced Diploma of Leadership and Management Diploma of Early Childhood Education and Care

The University of Sydney

2010 - 2014

Bachelor of Commerce

(Reference Letter from Ionata Digital is available upon request)